Guide to the New England Commission for United Ministries in Higher Education Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Financial Material, 1966-1973; Series VII
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1968 Mar (Box 25, Folder 251)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1968 Apr (Box 25, Folder 252)
  - 7 -Monthly accounts, 1968 May., Jun (Box 26, Folder 253)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1968 Jul, Aug (Box 26, Folder 254)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1968 Sep, Oct (Box 26, Folder 255)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1968 Nov (Box 26, Folder 256)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1968 Dec (Box 26, Folder 257)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1969 Jan, Feb (Box 26, Folder 258)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1969 Mar, Apr (Box 26, Folder 259)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1969 May, Jun (Box 26, Folder 260)
  - 7 -Monthly accounts, 1969 Jul, Aug (Box 26, Folder 261)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1969 Sep (Box 26, Folder 262)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1969 Oct (Box 26, Folder 263)
  - 7 -Monthly accounts, 1969 Nov (Box 27, Folder 264)
  - 7-Monthly accounts, 1969 Dec (Box 27, Folder 265)
  - 7-Monthly statements, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 266)
  - 7-Tax Records, 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 267)